

\boxtimes

shameermerican@gmail.com

•

+60 17-667-2821



Bandar Baru Bangi, Selangor, Malaysia



https://ahmadshameer.github.io/ahmadshameer.html

Educations

2019 - 2022



Degree in Music with Hons (Audio Production)

AKADEMI SENI BUDAYA DAN WARISAN KEBANGSAAN (ASWARA)

NATIONAL ACADEMY OF ARTS CULTURE AND HERITAGE (ASWARA)

Specialization : Audio Production
Major Instrument : Classical Piano
Minor Instrument : Modern Vocal

• Dean Listed in Semester 3 and 4

SOFTWARE USED:









- Logic Pro X
- Caraasband
- Musescore
- Adobe Audition CC

2015 - 2019

KZU

Diploma in Visual Effects Compositing (VFX) **KRU ACADEMY**

• Head of Student Secretary

SOFTWARE USED:













PF Track

Adobe After Effects CC

Adobe Premiere Pro CCBoris FX Mocha AE

AHMAD SHAMEER MERICAN BIN AHMAD SATAR

MIXING & MASTERING ENGINEER | MUSICIAN VIDEO EDITOR | VFX ARTIST | DESIGNER

Profile

My name is Ahmad Shameer Merican Bin Ahmad Satar. Born on 28 December 1999. Experienced in mixing and mastering songs, audio production, video editing, designing ,visual effects compositing and teaching. Multitasking person and likes to try and learn something new.

Work Experiences

2020 - 2021

Universal Music Malaysia Sdn. Bhd.

FREELANCE DESIGNER

• Design Instagram and Facebook filter for artists marketing and promotion

2019

Warner Music Malaysia (Domestic) Sdn. Bhd.

VIDEOGRAPHER

VIDEO EDITOR

DESIGNER

MARKETING

- Contributed ideas for digital marketing campaigns
- Shooting video for international and domestic artists promotion and marketing video
- Edit the videos to be publish on artists and Warner Music Malaysia social media

Part Time Work

2021

Covid-19 Vaccination Centre: Galaxy Mall Ampang, Malaysia **VOLUNTEER**

2019 - 2021

Part Time Private Music Tutor

ELECTRONIC KEYBOARD, PIANO & BASIC MUSIC THEORY TUTOR

Skills

Mixing & Mastering

Production

Audio



Teaching



AHMAD SHAMEER MERICAN **BIN AHMAD SATAR**

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS

WARNER MUSIC MALAYSIA SDN. BHD.



Shooting a content video with Lukas Graham for Warner Music Malaysia (International) marketing purposes.



Helping for backstage setup and preparation for Altimet: The Last Show concert and shooting videos for Warner Music Malaysia (Domestic) promotion and marketing.



PERFORMANCES



Performed for wedding with my band called IMAGINEXT MUSIC.



TECHNICAL



Performed Classical Piano in **ASWARA** Classical Recital twice in a semester from semester 1 until semester 4.

Do a recording, mixing and mastering for my version of cover song in a recording studio.



Stage Manager for 2nd **ASWARA** International Classical Piano & Voice Competition.



Setup the lighting for Recital Classical in ASWARA.

AHMAD SHAMEER MERICAN BIN AHMAD SATAR

CERTIFICATES

ASWARA DEAN LIST

YEAR 2, SEMESTER 2 20 AUGUST 2021

YEAR 2, SEMESTER 1
26 APRIL 2021

HEAD OF STUDENT SECRETARY

30 JULY 2018

CHARITY AND VOLUNTEER "SUMBANGAN BAKTI DI RUMAH WARGA EMAS" PUSAT JAGAAN AL-FIKHRAH MALAYSIA

9 JANUARY 2018

VOLUNTEER

PROGRAM UKHWAH CARE 2017
PONDOK MAHFUZAH BATANG KALI, SELANGOR, MALAYSIA
19 & 20 AUGUST 2017

COMMITTEE MEMBER (TEASER)

PROGRAM BEAUTY OF RAMADHAN 4.0 KRU ACADEMY
6 JUNE - 5 JULY 2016

SHORT FILM COMPETITION

PROGRAM BEAUTY OF RAMADHAN 4.0 KRU ACADEMY
WIN 3RD PLACE

6 JUNE - 5 JULY 2016

TRINITY COLLEGE LONDON

INITIAL - ELECTRONIC KEYBOARD WITH DISTINCTION
JUNE 2012

GRADE 1 - ELECTRONIC KEYBOARDS WITH DISTINCTIONNOVEMBER 2013

GRADE 2 - ELECTRONIC KEYBOARDS WITH DISTINCTIONMAY 2015

GRADE 4 - ELECTRONIC KEYBOARDS

NOVEMBER 2016